Contact

reidrm@yahoo.com

www.linkedin.com/in/renee-reid-bsn-rn-7a876277 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Pediatrics
Patient Education
PALS

Renee Reid, BSN, RN

Travel RN at Bellevue Hospital

Greater New York City Area

Summary

Registered Nurse with 4 years of administrative experience and 25 years of ER and critical care experience. Skilled in patient flow and bed board management. Skilled in Medication Administration, Pediatric Advanced Life Support (PALS), Advanced Cardiac Life Support (ACLS), Emergency Medicine, Critical Care and TNCC. Strong healthcare services professional with a BSN focused in Registered Nursing.

Experience

Nurses 24/7- LLC
Travel Nurse
June 2016 - Present (4 years 1 month)
Travel RN at Bellevue Hospital Emergency Department

BronxCare Health System
Patient Care Manager
June 2018 - September 2019 (1 year 4 months)

Mount Sinai Health System
Assistant Nurse Manager Emergency Department
October 2017 - May 2018 (8 months)

New York-Presbyterian Hospital Triage Coordinator June 2016 - October 2017 (1 year 5 months) Greater New York City Area

Medical Staffing Network
Travel RN
January 2009 - June 2016 (7 years 6 months)
Bellevue Hospital, NY, NY
Bronx Lebanon Hospital, Bronx, NY
Lincoln Medical and Mental Health, Bronx, NY
Page 1 of 2

Montefiore Einstein Division, Bronx, NY

UPMC

Critical Care RN
October 2009 - October 2013 (4 years 1 month)

Rapid Response RN

Critical care float pool.

Cross Country TravCorps

Travel RN

April 2007 - January 2009 (1 year 10 months)

ED at Hospital of the University of Pennsylvania, Philadelphia, PA

MICU at Johns Hopkins Hospital, Baltimore, MD

ED at North Shore Manhasset, Manhasset, NY

ED at Winthrop University Hopsital, Mineola, NY

ICU at Roy Lester Schneider Regional Hospital, USVI

CVICU at UCLA Medical Center, Los Angeles, NY

Education

Western Governors University
BSN, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2015 - 2016)

Western Pennsylvania Hospital School of Nursing
Diploma, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (1993 - 1995)